marinersoftware.com 2008-12-16

# Small Business Mac Software - Mariner Software Privacy Statement

Mariner Software Online Privacy Statement

At Mariner Software, we recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy is important to us; the information contained herein strives to help you understand just how much personal information is (and is not) collected on our web site and how it is used.

Automatic Information Collection

When navigating our web site, personal information about you is not collected automatically. On some of the pages on our site of our web site, we do log the IP address of your computer to enable verification of email addresses. This does not disclose any personal information about you.

About Cookies

As is the case with many web sites, certain portions of Mariner Software's web site may utilize a common technology known as "cookies" to collect and/or store information about you. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. We use cookies to store small bits of information about your browsers abilities to provide you with the best and most efficient experience possible.

E-mail Addresses and Their Usage

Mariner Software does not purchase or rent bulk email lists. We do ask that you enter your e-mail address on our download pages before downloading software. You always have the option to not provide your e-mail address. Mariner Software does not sell, trade or rent your email address to others. We ask for your e-mail address so that we may contact you to inform you of updates, special offers, or other software that we think would be of interest to you. When you participate in a contest, promotion or survey, we may ask for your name, address, e-mail address or other information. We know that the members of our e-mail list are very sensitive to receiving spam, or unsolicited email; hence we are very careful about what we send out and to whom.

Privacy Policies

Mariner Software's privacy policy is subject to change at any time. Mariner Software will provide notice 30 days prior to implementing any major changes to our privacy policy. Our web site contains links to other web sites and is not responsible for privacy practices of those web sites. We encourage users to learn about the privacy practices of those web sites.
